onlinewebsitesdesign.com 2014-09-28

# OWD | Committed to Protect the Privacy of its Customers

This privacy policy is developed for you to understand how we collect, use, link, disclose, and make use of your personal information. The terms, “we”, “us” and “our” refer to the Company (Online Websites Design ®). “You” refers to a user of our service. Your acceptance to our Privacy Policy reflects your consent to our collection, room, use, and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

## Information Collection and Use

Online Websites Design is the exclusive possessor of the data collected on this site. We will not trade, share, or charge this gathered data to others in different ways from what is disclosed in this statement. Information collected by us is relevant to internal management activities such as creating new accounts and billing.

In general, the information you provide is only used to help us communicate with you in response to questions, solicit feedback from users, providing technical support and informing about promotional offers.

## How we Protect your Data

Certain security measures are designed to protect your gathered data from illegal access. Your account password is meant to protect your account on this platform and we encourage you to take certain steps to maintain privacy for your personal information. Your data is further protected from security breaches through the implementation of technological security measures namely encryption, firewalls, and secure socket layer. These sort of measures do not guarantee complete protection from being accessed, altered, or destroyed due to the breach of any nature. Your use of our service acknowledges that you understand and agree to assume all sort of risks.

## Links to other websites

We possibly provide you with links or compatibility with other websites or applications. Please be aware that we are not accountable for the solitude practices of such websites or applications. We encourage our users to read the privacy statements of other website that collects personally identifiable information before proceeding to use them. Our website also includes social media features such as like and share buttons for Facebook or Twitter. These features may gather your IP address reflecting your visit on certain pages of our website. The privacy policy of company you are interacting with these features govern your interaction with these features.

## Security and Data Retention

We take every possible precautionary measures to protect information of our users. Your information is protected on this platform online and offline specifically when sensitive information is submitted to us. Once you submit your sensitive information while placing order with us, it is encrypted using SSL technology. We retain your information until your account is active. You can contact us if you no longer require your account being active or don’t want us to use your information.

## Special Offers

A verification email regarding password and username is sent from this platform to all new users.Registered members of this platform receive certain emails regarding our products, services, and promotions if they have selected to receive such mails from us. We also provide an option of unsubscribing from these sort of mails to reflect our respect for confidential information of users.

## Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information

If your personally identifiable information changes or you are not interested to receive our services, then you are provided with different ways to correct, update, or delete such data. For this purpose, you can email us at [info@onlinewebsitesdesign.com](mailto:info@onlinewebsitesdesign.com). To deactivate or delete your account, you can communicate with our customer representative and your query will be fulfilled within 30 days.

## Notification of Changes

We are authorized to modify this policy anytime and modifications will be uploaded on this page. You are requested to visit this page from time to time for being aware of any modifications and manner of using your gathered data.

## Business Transitions

In any event, Online Websites Design ® goes through a business change over such as mergers or acquisitions with other entity, your personally identifiable data will likely be included in the transferred assets. You will be informed via email for any such change in rights or control of your personal data.

## Legal Disclaimer

Though we make every possible step to maintain your confidentiality, we might need to disclose your personal data whenever required by law or to comply with legal procedures being served here.

## Contact Us

If you have any query or questions regarding this Privacy Policy or the practices of this Site, please contact us by sending an email to [info(at)onlinewebsitesdesign(dot)com](mailto:info@onlinewebsitesdesign.com). This Privacy Policy was updated on 11th January 2014.
